const data= [
    {
        question: "What is 5 + 3?",
        options: ["8", "7", "6", "9"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 - 4?",
        options: ["8", "9", "7", "6"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 6 * 7?",
        options: ["42", "48", "36", "30"],
        answer: "42"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 / 9?",
        options: ["8", "9", "10", "7"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 19?",
        options: ["44", "46", "42", "40"],
        answer: "44"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 - 37?",
        options: ["67", "68", "63", "62"],
        answer: "63"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 * 4?",
        options: ["60", "55", "45", "50"],
        answer: "60"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 / 8?",
        options: ["9", "8", "7", "6"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 30 + 45?",
        options: ["75", "70", "80", "65"],
        answer: "75"
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 - 7?",
        options: ["11", "10", "12", "9"],
        answer: "11"
    }
];

export default data;
